Here, we set up our TensorFlow variables.
ここで TensorFlow変数を 設定します
x is a placeholder that will store our input batches.
xは 入力バッチを 格納する プレースホルダーです
We initialize the batch size to None,
バッチサイズの 初期値を Noneにすると
which allows the placeholder to later accept a batch of any size,
プレースホルダーが どんなサイズのバッチでも 受け入れられるように なります
and we set the image dimensions to 32 by 32 by 1. y stores our labels.
画像の寸法を 32x32x1に 設定します  yには ラベルが 格納されます
In this case, our labels come through with sparse variables,
この例では ラベルは スパース変数を 渡します
which just means that they're integers.
スパース変数とは 整数で
They aren't one-hot encoded yet.
まだ ワンホットエンコーディングされていません
We use the tf.one_hot function to one-hot encode the labels.
tf.one_hot関数を 使って ラベルの ワンホットエンコーディングを 行います
Now we set up our training pipeline.
次に トレーニングパイプラインを 設定します
First, we have another hyperparameter to tune.
まず 別のハイパーパラメーターを 調整する 必要があります
The learning rate tells TensorFlow how quickly to update the network's weights.
学習率は TensorFlowに対し ネットワークの 重みを 更新するペースを 知らせます
0.001 is a good default value
0.001は デフォルト値として 悪くありませんが
but you can experiment with other rates and see how they do.
他の率なら どうなるかを 試してみても いいでしょう
Next, we pass the input data to the LeNet function to calculate our logits.
次に 入力データを LeNet関数に 渡して ロジットを 計算します
We used the tf.nn.softmax_cross_entropy_with_logits
tf.nn.softmax_cross_entropy_with_logits関数を
function to compare those logits to
これらのロジットを
the ground truth labels and calculate the cross entropy.
検証データラベルと比較し、クロスエントロピーを求めます
Cross entropy is just a measure of how different
クロスエントロピーはロジットが検証
the logits are from the ground truth training labels.
トレーニングラベルからどれだけ離れているかを示すに過ぎません
The tf.reduce_mean function averages the cross entropy from all of the training images.
tf.reduce_mean関数は すべてのトレーニング画像の クロスエントロピーを 平均します
AdamOptimizer uses the Adam algorithm to minimize
AdamOptimizerは Adamアルゴリズムを使って
the loss function similarly to what stochastic gradient descent does.
損失関数を 最小化します  確率的勾配降下法と 似ていますね
The Adam algorithm is a little more sophisticated than stochastic gradient descent,
Adamアルゴリズムは 確率的勾配降下法より 少し洗練されているので
so it's a good default choice for an optimizer.
デフォルトの オプティマイザーに 適しています
This is where we use the learning rate hyperparameter that we set earlier.
ここで 先ほど設定した 学習率ハイパーパラメーターを 使います
Finally, we run the minimize function on the optimizer which
最後に オプティマイザーに対して minimize関数を 実行します
uses backpropagation to update the network and minimize our training loss.
逆伝播で ネットワークが更新され トレーニング損失が 最小化されます
So this is our training pipeline.
これで トレーニングパイプラインが できました
But so far, it's only a pipeline,
でも これは パイプラインに 過ぎないので
we have to actually pass data into the pipeline for it to work.
機能させるためには 実際に データを 渡さなければなりません
We'll get to that in a few code cells.
それは いくつかの コードセルで 実行します